next up incoherent Len vulture Sarah
Palin uh the AL the Alaskan Rodeo Cyborg
came roaring back into the spotlight to
jump on the Trump wagon here she is
endorsing him back in
January looking around at all of you you
hardworking Iowa families you farm
families and teachers and teamsters
and Cooks you rock and rollers and holy
rollers you with the hands that rock the
[Applause]
cradle to Total courtesy smile for that
doll you hands that rock the cradle and
Girl Interrupted and single white
females and Jennifer E this is for all
the Rosemary's Babies and the airbuds
and the Big Trouble in Little China and
Fridays and next Fridays and especially
all you working hard down at the
roadhouse by Point Break this campaign
will never die
hard comedians where is Sarah palum now
April I don't know probably becoming a
grandmother for like the ninth time
cryst hate condom all right Point
Bo up to her tits and
pills Sarah pillin rone based off of her
sweater Joanne Fabrics yes
no that's not
it tell you exactly what happened a
disco ball got loose in Anchorage and
she hunted it and skinned it that is
what happened I use every part of the
disco ball every
part